<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on d3buggr</title>
    <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on d3buggr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright 2022. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://d3buggr.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s talk.</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/heart-to-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/heart-to-heart/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk.
I have been suffering and this is my outlet
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do with myself.
Or How to improve myself.
My life till now has been a single tone.
It has no highs and no lows.
I think I can describe it as always being at the lowest of all things.
I am not sure. what to improve on.
Not that many things interest me.
I am heavily addicted to porn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attention</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/attention/</guid>
      <description>No one in the social media would like you to know about this. Even if you are aware of it , no one will bring it up
In social media, the currency is attention.
In video games, the currency is attention.
In porn, the currency is attention.
In subpar relationships, the currency is attention.
If attention was a currency, how are you spending it?
This could determine everything in your life depending on how deep your attention has been robbed from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Necessity</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/necessity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 19:52:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/necessity/</guid>
      <description>growth is a necessity of life.
progression is a necessity of life.
sleep is a neccisity of life.
food and water are a necessity
social interactions are a necessity.
nicotine, caffeine, alcohol are not. video games are not. youtube and social media are not the only sources of social interactions and they are not necessity of life. drugs are not a necessity of life.
Make sure that you know what your necessities are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobby</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/hobby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 08:31:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/hobby/</guid>
      <description>I have been struggling to look for hobby.
I think I have finally begin to narrow it down.
First and foremost. Let&amp;rsquo;s establish what are the parameters of a good hobby.
It should be fun.
It should be destressing.
It should not cause pain afterwards.
It should not cause me to lose my mind in it.
&amp;ndash;
The Good Ones Book Reading
Travelling
Guitar Music Practice.
Journaling
Social Interactions ( Better done 1:1 ) / Discord / Dating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck in a Box</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/stuck-in-a-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 05:53:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/stuck-in-a-box/</guid>
      <description>There is a box. The box is made of glass.
So it gives the feeling that everyone should be able to see you.
The body feels tiny. But not that tiny compared to the box.
It&amp;rsquo;s very dark outside. There is no source of light other than a slight ray in the sky.
Yet there is enough light to figure out if someone is outside.
The box is small. There is no door or windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoking</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/smoking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 18:14:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/smoking/</guid>
      <description>Hi Guys, I have multiple addictions in life.. there has been weed , porn, games, social media scrolling.. I would say that I am a guy (26yo now) with many addictions. I like to work and have decent source of income but my free time gets consumed by these addictions a lot more than I would like them to be.
But here I wanted to post about my first ever conquer over a addiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Conversation</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/real-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/real-conversation/</guid>
      <description>We live in a time where more and more conversations can be broadcasted online.
We live in a time where more real time interactions can take place in a conversation.
And yet, what we are seeing is that less of these conversations are becoming less empathetic on social media.
Nobody is willing to see the other side of things especially when there is no reason to do that.
You can easily create your own safe space on social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karma</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/karma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:01:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/karma/</guid>
      <description>I just read the karma yoga chapter of the bhagvad gita and it started to rain.
according to what I thought I read, this rain like my body and my soul, are blessings from him.
So why should one work. cause if god ( if such a thing exist ) stops working then we are all doomed for sure. if it stops to rain, we don’t get any plants, nor any animals will be able to survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday!</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/sunday-21-03-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/sunday-21-03-2021/</guid>
      <description>Today is a sunday, so everyone should rest.
The whole world should stop doing whatever they are doing just because it is Sunday.
This is what we are told.
It&amp;rsquo;s been seven days. Seven times has the sun come up since then. The last time it came out.
That means, I can rest.
Feels like a weird logic. But why is this being told by everyone..
I want to rest. I need rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost Clarity</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/lost/</guid>
      <description>Why do the hard things still feel so hard to do.
I know that I procrastinate a lot and I still give up on 80% of my projects.
Because they are hard. There are too many unknowns.
There is no clear direction and I feel lost.
This is the hardest thing for me to find a way when there is no clear path.
Which makes me think if there is ever a clear path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literally Keeping It Simple!</title>
      <link>https://d3buggr.dev/post/keeping-it-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://d3buggr.dev/post/keeping-it-simple/</guid>
      <description>This is the last time I am creating a new Hugo block. This is the last time I try to change themes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s keep it simple from now on.
This is the last time I am updating Hugo.
You can say I am hard stuck on 0.79 from now on.
I am angry cause I am wasting time and I know it :P
See you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
